<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Porrith Suong</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Porrith Suong</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I graduated from City College of New York with a Bachelors in Science in Computer Science. I am an avid game developer highly interested in
 Optimizations and high performance computing Computer Graphics Game AI  I&amp;rsquo;ve built a bunch of small workflow tools within Unity and are opened source on Github. Feel free to take a look at various tools I built here.
My Work I founded my own development studio, initialPrefabs, where I primarily do:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Games</title>
      <link>/work/games/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/games/</guid>
      <description>Here are some of the games I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on over the past few years!
Table of Contents  Released  Kitty in the Box 2 Emissary the Sunsets the Self Bag of Beliefs Kart Microgame Kung Fu Kickball   Not Released  Inwards     Released Kitty in the Box 2 (Released, Mobile) Kitty in the Box 2 is a mobile game where you aid, Sushi our lovable cat, jump into boxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thousand Ant</title>
      <link>/work/thousandant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/thousandant/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Thousand Ant  Flocking With the C# Job System C# Job System: Using DOTs with Managed C# APIs   Unity Technologies  Kart Microgame Open Projects Devlg Bolt Adaptive Performance Physics Optimizations Shader Graph UI Toolkit Scriptable Objects ML Agents Device Simulator   Genvid Technologies  I work with Thousand Ant and create educational videos/technical scripts to explain new tech and features for their end users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting with Vulkan and Rust</title>
      <link>/blog/vulcan-rust-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/vulcan-rust-part-1/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to learn Rust and Vulkan together. I&amp;rsquo;ve done a bit of it before using C++ and Vulkan, but I&amp;rsquo;d like to start recreating that previous C++ Vulkan Renderer with Rust. So in these series of blog posts - I&amp;rsquo;ll write some public notes on Rust and how it is interfaced with the Vulkan ash crate.
The implementation of Vulkan will primarily be based on this tutorial. This blog post will cover the Instance section of the tutorial series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UGUIDots Progress Report</title>
      <link>/blog/making-of-uguidots/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/making-of-uguidots/</guid>
      <description>UGUIDOTS is a data oriented workflow of Unity default runtime UI, UGUI. This provides a conversion workflow to convert the authored GameObject UI to a more DOTS friendly UI system, that works with their Universal Render Pipeline (formerly known as Lightweight Render Pipeline).
 While UIElements certainly scales better and a DOTS version is in the works, I wanted to solve my current issues and have a good understanding of the UI Pipeline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Scriptable Render Pipeline</title>
      <link>/work/custom-srp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/custom-srp/</guid>
      <description>The Custom Scriptable Render Pipeline is an ongoing project to create my own render pipeline to use in Unity for future projects.
Github Link
   Feature     Rendering Various Layers    Batching Multiple Spheres    Lighting with PBR rendering     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DANI AI</title>
      <link>/work/dani-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/dani-ai/</guid>
      <description>Dani AI is a node based editor to help design and prototype AI in Unity. Each AI designed and built using Dani AI follows a neural network like schema and attempts to treat each agent as an organism with senses that update in realtime.
Senses provide natural information about the simulated world and hook into decisions, where the agent executes a series of authored actions from the user.
You can grab it here on the Asset Store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reactive Disposal</title>
      <link>/work/reactivedisposal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/reactivedisposal/</guid>
      <description>Reactive Disposal is really just a small layer on top of Unity&amp;rsquo;s Entity Component System to dispose unmanaged memory. This is not the same as a garbage collector as it does not do it automatically - the dispose function must still be called but this reduces the amount of code needed to write the same functionality over and over again.
Github Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UGUIDots</title>
      <link>/work/uguidots/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/uguidots/</guid>
      <description>UGUIDots is an on going project to convert Unity&amp;rsquo;s default UI to a data oriented compliant system. The system is meant to augment on top of Unity&amp;rsquo;s UI.
Currently, the only features supported are:
 Simple image rendering Text rendering Render orders Static Analysis for batching Button States  Button closing   Image Effects interfaced with Universal Render Pipeline Shaders Scaling &amp;amp; Anchoring Text support through char pointers  Github Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ten Months into the Making of Repurposed</title>
      <link>/blog/ten-months-into-the-making/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/ten-months-into-the-making/</guid>
      <description>So just a bit of background information, Repurposed is a 2D action arena game with heavy card game elements. I think videos do more justice at the moment instead of me pitching, so here&amp;rsquo;s the actual gameplay video link:
Around ten months ago, October of 2018, I prototyped a game idea on Google Slides on how I wanted people to play the game, and entered it into Unity&amp;rsquo;s 2D challenge. But, considering we only had 3 months and the game was very quite large for the scope of the challenge, I turned the game into a much larger vision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scaffolding in Development</title>
      <link>/blog/low-level-apis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/low-level-apis/</guid>
      <description>So I preferably enjoy working with low level APIs instead of high level APIs. The main reason behind that is the amount of control I have as a developer, especially on creating the functionality I need. So if there is an alternative API which provides a lower level solution than a high level API which does exactly what I need&amp;hellip;
I would still go for the lower level solution, even if I have to recreate the same functionality as the high level API.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
