<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Porrith Suong</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>psuong.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="psuong.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2015 19:41:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2015 19:41:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Manage?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;So it’s been a long time since I’ve actually decided to write a blog. I’d say I would keep my portfolio updated
but that hasn’t actually happened that often, since I lead a very crazy lifestyle. This post isn’t going to be a &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;“how
to be a success X,”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; but really some things that I’ll highlight that can help you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;really-so-who-am-i&quot;&gt;Really, so who am I?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So if you know me, you’ll know me as the current ACM President of ACM at City College and a 3rd year Computer Science student. But if you’re a close friend, then you know that outside of the college, I actively work on my own start up company &lt;a href=&quot;http://bit.ly/ugfstudio_&quot;&gt;UGF Studio&lt;/a&gt;. I won’t go through what my start up does, because that’s beyond the scope of this blog post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;managing-your-time&quot;&gt;Managing your time&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s be honest, it’s the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;most important&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;obvious&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; skill that we’ll all breeze over. There are tons of tools to help with time management, such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://trello.com/&quot;&gt;Trello&lt;/a&gt; or even a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/calendar&quot;&gt;Google Calendar&lt;/a&gt;. These tools are there to help you, but if you’re not actively using them, those tools will “suck.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“Grab the lowest hanging fruit!”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a common phrase and what it says is that you should be doing the task that’s the most immediate and easy to do. You wouldn’t go picking up a fruit at the highest point of a tree, it’s too much work and resources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don’t do everything.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do things one at a time, there’s no point in multitasking if the work that comes out of it is crap. (Maybe that can apply for schoolwork, but don’t push it!) Couple this up with grabbing the lowest hanging fruit. If you do things one at a time, you’ll be a bit more organized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;learn-to-take-hits&quot;&gt;Learn to take hits&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s something called &lt;em&gt;opportunity costs&lt;/em&gt; and people generally don’t think about it all the time. With the semester rolling in, it’s easy to say, “I won’t have time because of X class.” To put that into perspective, there will be x number of people who will drop out of a project. Some for legitimate reasons, some due to time management issues, etc. A project outside of class is something to put on your resume and provides experiences not taught in class. A class teaches students skills focused around a particular subject. Both can be seen as equally important, but I’ll say this straight, grades aren’t the &lt;strong&gt;most super important factor&lt;/strong&gt;. If you’re not using what you learned in class, the class would be considered useless useless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;general-tips&quot;&gt;General Tips&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So on ACM, especially for gamedev, I made a Slack account and invited partipants into the team. Utilize that often, since that’s a community that can provide help. There are certain channels like #general, where you can ask for help about anything. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Of course, don’t spam.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; The Facebook group is also a means of resource. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Again, don’t spam.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Use that if you’re not on our Slack team. Fatigue will come, don’t worry about that because it’s natural for people to get fatigue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-do-i-do-it&quot;&gt;How do I do it?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Really, what’s up there. Nothing really special about this section.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;cheers&quot;&gt;Cheers,&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;porrith-suong&quot;&gt;Porrith Suong&lt;/h3&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>psuong.github.io/management</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">psuong.github.io/management</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Project/Porfolio Launch</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Portfolio launch! On my portfolio I will post projects I am working on and worked on.
Additionally I will keep my portfolio updated ranging from tools/3D models in Unity
to projects worked on at the City College of New York. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;first-projectportfolio-launch&quot;&gt;First Project/Portfolio Launch&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently, on my portfolio I only have posted my final project to my Python class.
I attempted to crack hashed passwords in three different files, with different
hash functions. Although, Yahoo in the past used no hash functions on the actual
passwords, Linkedin and Formsprings used SHA-1 and SHA-256 hash functions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the project is not too difficult, I attempted to determine the passwords
efficiently, using my knowledge of Python’s file i/o and data structures (hash
table/dictionaries) to efficiently determine the passwords. Out of the 10,000 passwords
cracked in Linkedin, I was only able to find approximately 7,000 potential passwords.
Yahoo was relatively easy, but Formsprings was the most difficult because of the way
they hash the function. Formsprings currently does not work and I will eventually
find a way to efficiently crack the password.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;whats-to-come&quot;&gt;What’s to come?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will continuously update my portfolio with projects and images of renders I work on
in Blender.
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ugfstudio.com&quot; title=&quot;Other works&quot;&gt;For more works I’ve contributed to, please check UGF Studio.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>psuong.github.io/firstpost</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">psuong.github.io/firstpost</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
