<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Porrith Suong</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>psuong.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="psuong.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2015 23:29:42 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2015 23:29:42 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Project/Porfolio Launch</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Portfolio launch! On my portfolio I will post projects I am working on and worked on.
Additionally I will keep my portfolio updated ranging from tools/3D models in Unity
to projects worked on at the City College of New York. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;first-projectportfolio-launch&quot;&gt;First Project/Portfolio Launch&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently, on my portfolio I only have posted my final project to my Python class.
I attempted to crack hashed passwords in three different files, with different
hash functions. Although, Yahoo in the past used no hash functions on the actual
passwords, Linkedin and Formsprings used SHA-1 and SHA-256 hash functions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the project is not too difficult, I attempted to determine the passwords
efficiently, using my knowledge of Python’s file i/o and data structures (hash
table/dictionaries) to efficiently determine the passwords. Out of the 10,000 passwords
cracked in Linkedin, I was only able to find approximately 7,000 potential passwords.
Yahoo was relatively easy, but Formsprings was the most difficult because of the way
they hash the function. Formsprings currently does not work and I will eventually
find a way to efficiently crack the password.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;whats-to-come&quot;&gt;What’s to come?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will continuously update my portfolio with projects and images of renders I work on
in Blender.
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ugfstudio.com&quot; title=&quot;Other works&quot;&gt;For more works I’ve contributed to, please check UGF Studio.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>psuong.github.io/firstpost</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">psuong.github.io/firstpost</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
